Papers of L. Marguerite Collier 1884-1977 (bulk 1935-1959)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Photographs and Negatives, undated; Series VIII
  - Negatives, undated; Subseries 6
    - Four 4x5 black and white negatives of photographs in other subseries, undated (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Books and Journals, undated; Series IX
  Five of 31 books belonging to Collier but not previously indexed; six issues of Anuario de la Sociedad Folklorica de Mexico. Editions of most items above were already in the Special Collections book collection. Twenty-six books from the Collier collection not previously in Special Collections have been added to the book collection of the repository. Items are arranged by author, followed by journals, chronologically.
  - Covarrubias, Miguel. Mexico South: The Isthmus of Tehuantepec, third printing. New York: Alfred A. Knopf, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - Keech, Roy A. Children Sing in New Mexico. Clarendon, Texas: The Clarendon Press, 1941 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Lea, Aurora Lucero-White. Literary Folklore of the Hispanic Southwest. San Antonio: The Naylor Company, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Marquez, Luis (photographer). Mexican Folklore, with text by Justino Fernandez. Mexico, D.F.: Editorial Fischgrund, no date. Annotated by Collier. Binding damaged. Stored in a folder at the beginning of this series., undated (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Pesman, M. Walter. Meet Flora Mexicana. Globe, Arizona: Dale Stuart Kino, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 39)
  - Anuario de la Sociedad Folklorica de Mexico, V.1 (1942), V.2 (1942), V.3 (1943), V.5 (1945), V.6 (1947), V.6 (1949) (Box 6, Folder 40-45)